educationquizzes.com 2015-06-07

# KS3 (Key Stage 3) Education Quizzes - Privacy Policy

This document outlines the Privacy Policy of Education Quizzes and forms an integral part of our Terms and Conditions.   

In order for us to maintain a record for you of the quizzes you have played (dates and scores) we need to retain the information that you give us at the time you register or subscribe. We acknowledge that you need to trust us when you share personal information with us and we take our responsibilities in this regard very seriously. We have documented below the ways in which we use the information that you give us.

**1\. Sharing Information**  
We will never share your information and therefore you will never be contacted by any third party as a result of information that you supply to us.

**2\. E-mails**  
We thoroughly disapprove of spam and we have no intention of subjecting you to unwanted and unsolicited e-mails. We want to provide you with enough information to keep you informed but not so much as to become annoying. We will send you a welcome e-mail when you subscribe. Other than that we will send e-mails only when we have something worthwhile to say that we genuinely think you might want to know about. After the initial welcome email, every time we email you we will give you the opportunity to be removed from our email list.

**3\. Information That We Hold About You**  
All of the information we hold about you can be found by logging into “Your Account” at the Education Quizzes website. You can change some of these details if you would like to do so. We do not store financial details about you such as your credit card or debit card details. Our merchant provider (PayPal) need to store some information that enables them to collect the monthly subscription. 

**4\. Cookies**  
Cookies are small computer files that assist both you and us. Without cookies it is not possible for us to keep a record for you of the quizzes you have played, the dates they were played and your scores. You have our assurance that under no circumstances will cookies be used to gather specific information about your use of the site either for our own use or for disclosure to any third party.

**5\. Place Of Processing**  
All personal information is held on and processed by computers situated in the UK.

**6\. Security**  
We have security procedures in place to protect our customer database and access to this database is restricted internally. It is the customer’s responsibility to protect their Username and Password to prevent unauthorized access to their account.

**7\. Removal From Our Database**  
You may e-mail us to request that your details be removed from our database at any time and we will immediately comply with your wishes.

**8\. Personal Data Retention Period**  
We will retain your personal details for one year from the last time that you use the website or we receive a communication from you to tell us to delete your data. This one year period allows you to regain your records (quizzes played, scores and dates) if your subscription lapses and you later decide to re-subscribe. 

**9\. Quiz Playing Data Retention**  
We reserve the right to remove your quiz playing records at any time but if this becomes necessary we will always try to tell you the reasons at least 30 days in advance.

**10\. Data Protection Information**  
You can obtain information about the data protection laws by visiting the Information Commissioner’s website at [www.dataprotection.gov.uk](http://www.dataprotection.gov.uk/); you can also search for our Data Protection Notification at the same place.
